Baby
I’m just trying to play it cool
But I just can’t hide that
I want you
Wait a minute 이게 뭐지?
내 심장이 lub-dub
자꾸만 뛰어
저 멀리서도 oh my gosh!
끌어당겨 you’re my crush!
초능력처럼
거대한 자석이 된 것만 같아 my heart
네 모든 게 내 맘에 달라붙어버려 boy
We’re magnetized 인정할게
This time I want
You You You You like it’s magnetic
U U U U U U U U super 이끌림
BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE
Dash-da-da Dash-da-da Dash-da
Like it’s magnetic
BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE
Dash-da-da Dash-da-da
Baby don’t say no
정반대 같아 our type
넌 J 난 완전 P
S와 N 극이지만
그래서 끌리지
내가 만들래 green light
여잔 배짱이지
So let’s go let’s go
Let’s go let’s go
숨기고 싶지 않아 자석 같은 my heart
내 맘의 끌림대로 너를 향해 갈게 boy
We’re magnetized 인정할게
This time I want
You You You You like it’s magnetic
U U U U U U U U super 이끌림
No push and pull
전속력으로 너에게 갈게
(In a rush in a rush)
Our chemistry
난 과몰입해 지금 순간에
(Baby you’re my crush you’re my crush)
No push and pull
네게 집중 후회는 안 할래
(Gonna dash gonna dash)
Never holding back
직진해 yeah
This time I want
You You You You like it’s magnetic
U U U U U U U U super 이끌림
BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE
Dash-da-da Dash-da-da Dash-da
Like it’s magnetic
BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE
Dash-da-da Dash-da-da
Baby don’t say no